{
  "1": {
    "question": "May I inquire, my dear sir/lady, how would you prefer to immortalize your precious travel memories?",
    "option_1": {
      "answer": "Take photos as much as possible! Posting on social media is all about travel.",
      "calculation": {
        "1": { "type": "modern", "point": 2 },
        "2": { "type": "spending", "point": 1 }
      }
    },
    "option_2": {
      "answer": "Let's take it with our own eyes. Photos are just things in an electronic device.",
      "calculation": {
        "1": { "type": "relaxed", "point": 1 },
        "2": { "type": "saving", "point": 1 }
      }
    }
  },
  "2": {
    "question": "How would you like to fill your journey with, my dear?",
    "option_1": {
      "answer": "We paid all the way here. Experience everything that we can.",
      "calculation": {
        "1": { "type": "energetic", "point": 2 },
        "2": { "type": "planned", "point": 2 },
        "3": { "type": "modern", "point": 1 }
      }
    },
    "option_2": {
      "answer": "Travel is a form of relaxation. Letâ€™s take time and fully enjoy this moment.",
      "calculation": {
        "1": { "type": "relaxed", "point": 2 },
        "2": { "type": "spontaneous", "point": 1 }
      }
    }
  },
  "3": {
    "question": "Might I ask, what is your esteemed approach to dining whilst traversing the world?",
    "option_1": {
      "answer": "Proven restaurants with high ratings and lots of reviews. Fine dining or Instagrammable restaurants are a plus.",
      "calculation": {
        "1": { "type": "modern", "point": 2 },
        "2": { "type": "spending", "point": 2 },
        "3": { "type": "cautious", "point": 1 }
      }
    },
    "option_2": {
      "answer": "Live like a local, eat like a local. Enjoy authentic flavors and experiences in local restaurants or street food vendors.",
      "calculation": {
        "1": { "type": "authentic", "point": 2 },
        "2": { "type": "saving", "point": 2 },
        "3": { "type": "risk", "point": 1 }
      }
    }
  },
  "4": {
    "question": "Apologies sir/lady, I could not prepare private limousine for the trip. How would you prefer to travel around?",
    "option_1": {
      "answer": "Save money, we have strong legs! Walking and buses help me see the city like a local.",
      "calculation": {
        "1": { "type": "energetic", "point": 1 },
        "2": { "type": "saving", "point": 2 },
        "3": { "type": "authentic", "point": 1 }
      }
    },
    "option_2": {
      "answer": "Save time and energy. I am willing to spend more money on taxi and private tours for a relaxing exploration.",
      "calculation": {
        "1": { "type": "relaxed", "point": 1 },
        "2": { "type": "spending", "point": 2 },
        "3": { "type": "modern", "point": 1 }
      }
    }
  },
  "5": {
    "question": "For what noble purpose do you embark on this journey, my dear?",
    "option_1": {
      "answer": "Shop and buy and purchase. List out the MUST-BUY things in this country.",
      "calculation": {
        "1": { "type": "modern", "point": 2 },
        "2": { "type": "spending", "point": 2 }
      }
    },
    "option_2": {
      "answer": "Visit all the landmarks. In this internet-developed generation, you can get all the stuff via online shopping.",
      "calculation": {
        "1": { "type": "saving", "point": 1 },
        "2": { "type": "authentic", "point": 1 }
      }
    }
  },
  "6": {
    "question": "Dear sir/lady, when it comes to your journeys, do you prefer to follow your heart in the moment or meticulously plan ahead for efficiency?",
    "option_1": {
      "answer": "My legs follow my heart. I would decide what to do depending on what I want to do at that moment.",
      "calculation": {
        "1": { "type": "spontaneous", "point": 2 },
        "2": { "type": "energetic", "point": 1 },
        "3": { "type": "risk", "point": 1 }
      }
    },
    "option_2": {
      "answer": "No plan, no action. I would plan everything ahead and strictly follow it to increase efficiency.",
      "calculation": {
        "1": { "type": "planned", "point": 2 },
        "2": { "type": "cautious", "point": 1 }
      }
    }
  },
  "7": {
    "question": "When would you like me to wake you up my dear sir/lady?",
    "option_1": {
      "answer": "Rise and shine! I love starting my day early with a packed schedule to make the most of every moment.",
      "calculation": {
        "1": { "type": "energetic", "point": 2 },
        "2": { "type": "planned", "point": 2 }
      }
    },
    "option_2": {
      "answer": "Slow mornings are the best. I enjoy a leisurely breakfast and taking my time to ease into the day.",
      "calculation": {
        "1": { "type": "relaxed", "point": 2 },
        "2": { "type": "spontaneous", "point": 1 }
      }
    }
  },
  "8": {
    "question": "Though it may not compare to the palace you reside in, what type of accommodation do you prefer the most during your travels?",
    "option_1": {
      "answer": "Budget-friendly all the way. Hostels or Airbnb give me the local vibe without breaking the bank.",
      "calculation": {
        "1": { "type": "saving", "point": 2 },
        "2": { "type": "authentic", "point": 2 }
      }
    },
    "option_2": {
      "answer": "Luxury is key. I prefer staying in boutique hotels or resorts for a comfortable and pampered experience.",
      "calculation": {
        "1": { "type": "spending", "point": 2 },
        "2": { "type": "modern", "point": 2 }
      }
    }
  },
  "9": {
    "question": "How do you elegantly handle unforeseen changes in your travel plans, dear sir/lady?",
    "option_1": {
      "answer": "Go with the flow! I adapt quickly and find new plans to keep the adventure going.",
      "calculation": {
        "1": { "type": "spontaneous", "point": 2 },
        "2": { "type": "risk", "point": 1 }
      }
    },
    "option_2": {
      "answer": "Stick to the script. I try to follow the original plan as closely as possible to avoid disruptions.",
      "calculation": {
        "1": { "type": "planned", "point": 2 },
        "2": { "type": "cautious", "point": 1 }
      }
    }
  },
  "10": {
    "question": "My sir/lady, it is getting late. How would you like to spend the night? Sleeping late can damage your delicate skin?",
    "option_1": {
      "answer": "Nightlife explorer. I enjoy checking out the local entertainment and vibrant nightlife.",
      "calculation": {
        "1": { "type": "energetic", "point": 2 },
        "2": { "type": "modern", "point": 1 }
      }
    },
    "option_2": {
      "answer": "Quiet evenings. I prefer relaxing at the hotel or finding a peaceful spot to unwind.",
      "calculation": {
        "1": { "type": "relaxed", "point": 2 },
        "2": { "type": "authentic", "point": 1 },
        "3": { "type": "cautious", "point": 1 }
      }
    }
  },
  "11": {
    "question": "Of course, there are ten guards for my sir/lady, but how would you like to handle travel insurance?",
    "option_1": {
      "answer": "A must-have! Travel insurance is essential for peace of mind on every trip.",
      "calculation": {
        "1": { "type": "planned", "point": 2 },
        "2": { "type": "saving", "point": 1 },
        "3": { "type": "cautious", "point": 2 }
      }
    },
    "option_2": {
      "answer": "Not for me. I see it as an unnecessary expense and prefer to take my chances.",
      "calculation": {
        "1": { "type": "spontaneous", "point": 2 },
        "2": { "type": "spending", "point": 1 },
        "3": { "type": "risk", "point": 2 }
      }
    }
  },
  "12": {
    "question": "My lady/sir, how many luggages would you like to take?",
    "option_1": {
      "answer": "Travel light. I pack only the essentials to keep things simple and easy.",
      "calculation": {
        "1": { "type": "spontaneous", "point": 1 },
        "2": { "type": "risk", "point": 1 }
      }
    },
    "option_2": {
      "answer": "Be prepared! I pack for every possible scenario to ensure I'm ready for anything.",
      "calculation": {
        "1": { "type": "planned", "point": 1 },
        "2": { "type": "cautious", "point": 1 }
      }
    }
  },
  "13": {
    "question": "When encountering the local populace, how does your majesty choose to engage with grace and charm?",
    "option_1": {
      "answer": "I love engaging in conversations and learning about the local culture.",
      "calculation": {
        "1": { "type": "energetic", "point": 1 },
        "2": { "type": "authentic", "point": 1 },
        "3": { "type": "risk", "point": 1 }
      }
    },
    "option_2": {
      "answer": "Keep it minimal. I focus on my own experience and keep interactions with locals to a minimum.",
      "calculation": {
        "1": { "type": "relaxed", "point": 1 },
        "2": { "type": "modern", "point": 1 },
        "3": { "type": "cautious", "point": 1 }
      }
    }
  },
  "14": {
    "question": "Dear sir/lady, in matters of exploration, how does your esteemed self perceive the significance of off-the-beaten-path destinations?",
    "option_1": {
      "answer": "Thrill of the unknown! I seek out hidden gems and unexplored territories to enrich my travel experiences.",
      "calculation": {
        "1": { "type": "risk", "point": 2 },
        "2": { "type": "authentic", "point": 2 }
      }
    },
    "option_2": {
      "answer": "Stick to the classics. I prefer well-known attractions and popular destinations for a familiar and comfortable journey.",
      "calculation": {
        "1": { "type": "cautious", "point": 2 },
        "2": { "type": "modern", "point": 2 }
      }
    }
  },
  "15": {
    "question": "In the realm of cultural exploration, how does your distinguished self prefer to unravel the tapestry of local traditions and customs?",
    "option_1": {
      "answer": "Immerse in traditions! I seek out cultural festivals and hands-on experiences to deeply connect with the heritage of the destination.",
      "calculation": {
        "1": { "type": "authentic", "point": 2 },
        "2": { "type": "risk", "point": 1 }
      }
    },
    "option_2": {
      "answer": "Appreciate from afar. I enjoy visiting museums and historical sites to gain insights into the culture without fully participating.",
      "calculation": {
        "1": { "type": "modern", "point": 1 },
        "2": { "type": "cautious", "point": 1 }
      }
    }
  }
}
